♪
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
Summer vacation.
Beautiful clouds.
And the sand!
I'm really at the beach!
[gasps]
With so many people!
[AYUMI]
Hey, Uka!
Hope this wasn't too
last minute for you.
-No!
-Kinda spur of the moment.
I wonder
how many people showed up.
[awkward chuckle]
Lost track after ten.
[AYUMI]
Hm. You good?
♪
[UKA]
They're goddesses.
All of them.
-I can't look head-on.
-[SERINA] Something wrong?
Hold up.
No swimsuit?
Even if I had one,
I'd be too nervous to wear it.
[KIYOSHI]
Yep, that tracks.
Right, Kai?
Hm?
♪
[gasps]
[KAI]
Why'd you look away?
Oh, I, uh...
I just don't know
where to look...
Right here!
Okay.
[KAI]
Come find me in a few.
[UKA]
Yeah.
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
I'm in love with him.
I can't deny that.
[waves crashing]
I have to move forward.
SPARKLE 8
SUMMON THE COURAGE
-[cheering]
-[water splashes]
[laughter]
♪
Hey!
[Ayumi panting]
[Ayumi sighs]
[AYUMI]
I'm freakin' parched!
[UKA]
Welcome back.
Hey. Do you guys
wanna get some drinks...
-Ugh. [groans]
-[gasps]
[YURU]
Why's Oguni here, of all days?
That sucks!
[MIHO]
Yeah.
They're glaring daggers.
♪
We cannot let 'em
mess with Serina.
You can count on me!
-You sure?
-Yeah!
That sounds perfect for you!
Like you stood up for her
with those other girls.
The rest of us
will stay out of it.
[KAI]
You'll stay out of it, too.
[all gasp]
I'll take care of it.
It's not her business.
♪
Oh? And who are you
to decide what's her business?
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have butted in.
In that case,
I'm gonna wander around
for a while.
♪
[gasps]
Wait up!
I'm scared we'll get separated
if we don't have a way
to contact you!
-Huh.
-[AYUMI] How about this.
I can lend you
my phone till you get back!
Huh? Wait, you actually
have a cell phone?
-[UKA] Mm-hmm.
-[AYUMI] What the...
How come you never told me?
We've gotta trade numbers!
♪
AYUMI ENDOU SERINA
KANNO
[chuckles]
All right. I'll go
and put you in my phone
as one of my special clubmates.
You're in a club?
Uh, the Kai Club.
[chuckles]
-Ugh.
-[AYUMI] With two members?
[SERINA] Yeah!
We sure don't need more.
[UKA] I'm sorry that
I'm the other member.
[groans]
Quit looking so bummed.
You remember
what I told you before?
-Be loud and proud!
-Hm.
We're loud and we're proud.
[both chuckle]
There!
All good!
[laughter]
[gulping]
[YASUSHI]
Hey, Kai!
I heard at the culture festival
you touched Ishimori's face
and lovingly stroked it!
[spits]
[coughs]
Fess up.
Did that happen?
[KAI]
There was no stroking.
[KIYOSHI]
Okay. But why her?
Aren't you only
caretaking during school?
I'm doing what, now?
[YASUSHI]
This isn't fair to Kanno!
Who cares?
You protect one girl,
then the other.
-[gasps]
-Do you want Kanno or Ishimori?
Make up your mind!
Nah. Seems clear to me.
There's only been one
he's really trying to protect.
Though he's still managed
to find a way
to give them both
the wrong idea.
♪
[UKA]
Look at that.
It's been a while
since I've seen the ocean.
Not since my parents took me
my first year of junior high.
I was too scared
of seeing people
from my school.
Kept making excuses.
And we stopped coming.
Back then, I thought
I would live my whole life
running from places like this.
And everywhere else.
-[REMI] Ishimori?
-[gasps]
-[whimpering]
-Huh?
♪
[shudders]
Why the heck's she here?
Last person I wanted to see
over summer break.
Imagine seeing a girl
like that in a swimsuit!
[REMI'S FRIEND 1A]
I'd barf.
[UKA]
And it's all happening again.
Just like I thought.
Honest.
Caring.
Courageous.
[UKA]
No more running.
I'll take the first step.
-Hey!
-Huh?
Um. Hello there.
Uh, how have you been?
Huh?
Dude, you think
we're friends after
what happened last time?
Hell, no.
Let's go!
[UKA] [gasps]
Wait.
Please hold on a second!
What do you want, freak?
Weirdo!
Get away from me!
[UKA] No.
I can't give up!
I've changed
so much since then!
You know, I don't remember
seeing you around school,
lately!
-Huh?
-[panting]
[REMI]
'Cause I dropped out.
Didn't feel comfortable
being around there with you.
[UKA]
I had no idea.
I don't understand,
but I'm sorry.
You got a problem?
[UKA]
No, I swear!
What are you up to now?
Nothin' much.
Trying to enjoy my life.
That sounds nice.
[MASASHI'S FRIEND 2A]
Who's that? Feels like
I've seen her before.
Oh. From Remi's class, huh?
♪
See you.
[UKA]
Just stay calm.
I'm okay.
Wait, that means...
Is Kai Miura here, too?
-Over there.
-[all gasp]
Oh, crap.
[REMI'S FRIEND 1A]
He still talks to you?
[REMI]
Interesting.
You're making things
happen, aren't you?
Uh, yeah! Exactly!
'Kay, chill out.
You're not quite the nuisance
you were before.
Still, not like I give a damn.
-[chuckles]
-Why did that make you happy?
[chuckles]
[AYUMI] Whoa!
Did you guys see that?
Aren't those the people
who used to bully her
back in junior high?
[AYUMI] I was gonna
try to give her a hand,
but she's got it covered.
[YURU] Our girl's
killin' it out there.
[SERINA]
I'm impressed.
I need to move on
from my past, too.
Maybe today could be the day.
-Kai...
-[KAI] Serina.
You got a sec?
[waves crashing]
♪
I already know
what you're planning to say.
So do you mind if I go first?
Honestly.
I still never really
got over you, Kai.
We both know how you are.
It's so impossible to tell
what you're thinking.
That's why
I had gotten the wrong idea.
The way you were acting
before break made me think
you still cared about me
as well.
But I understand.
You only did that
for Uka's sake.
To keep her out
of the crossfire.
So before we leave,
can I ask you what I was
too scared to ask back then?
♪
Kai.
Did you ever have
feelings for me?
♪
I loved you.
[gasps]
[SERINA]
Kai...I need you.
But, you don't need me.
But after what you said,
I had to let you go.
That's my answer.
♪
Yeah.
I knew that, obviously!
Ya silly!
Well, I've gotta head home.
♪
Goodbye.
And thank you.
♪
[whimpering]
[sobs]
[sniffles]
♪
[ALL]
Ah.
[gasps]
[groans]
[YASUSHI]
So, uh...
We're sorry, Serina.
Uh. But still,
did he really have to be
so harsh with that last part?
Yes.
Thanks to that.
I can finally give up on him.
♪
Uh?
So, you good now?
[Yasushi panting]
[YASUSHI] Bro! What the hell
are you thinking,
rejecting Kanno?
What?
No way!
[UKA]
What?
But why would he reject her?
[UKA] Miura.
What happened?
Something that
isn't your business.
Yes, it is!
It is.
Maybe you're right.
Still...
you can't choose
how other people feel.
So let it be.
Don't bother racking
your brain over it.
♪
[SERINA]
And, sent.
To Miura?
Nah. To Uka.
She'd get worried
if I left without saying.
Why has everything been
about Ishimori lately?
Why would he pick her?
It doesn't make any sense!
You'll get it
once you know her.
[MIHO]
I highly doubt that.
[groans]
With him,
I had lost my strength.
[phone vibrates]
But in her case, she found it.
She went home?
♪
[phone chimes]
Lemme respond
to Uka real...quick.
[moans]
Uh.
♪
-[chuckles]
-[gasps]
What'd you say to make her
write that novel?
[SERINA]
Here.
I'll let you see for yourself.
♪
Oh. That's it?
[chuckles]
Yeah.
There's nothing else
for me to say!
She knows what it means.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE
THE OTHER MEMBER, UKA!
[UKA]
You're so sweet,
but I should say this to you.
♪
[phone vibrates]
Uh!
[chuckles]
[UKA]
It's from Ayumi!
I FINALLY FINISHED MY HOMEWORK!
AM I A GOOD GIRL?
GIVE ME COMPLIMENTS!
She's always adorable.
Right. I should reply.
GOOD GIRL!
Are we close enough for this?
Well...let's try!
♪
[phone vibrates]
Ah.
YAY!!
[UKA]
I've gotten more comfortable
texting Ayumi and Serina.
They're both so different.
But still, I feel like
I know them better now.
Ayumi likes it
when you dote on her.
Whereas
Serina is very involved.
Honestly, I don't
quite understand
why she concerns herself
with stuff like this.
♪
If I want his number,
I need to ask him.
So we need to hang out.
Easy, right?
But how do I get him
to meet up with me?
I could say I wanna
hang out to get his number.
Straightforward.
Though I don't see
how he benefits from that.
I don't know.
I haven't even asked
Ayumi or Serina to meet up yet.
I'm so socially anxious.
I can't remember.
Was I always like this?
Stop right there!
Don't let the bad
thoughts win!
I should go for a walk!
♪
Hey, are you going somewhere?
The bookstore.
[UKA'S DAD]
If you want, I can take you.
I'm all right.
[UKA'S DAD] Well, be sure
to take your phone.
I've got it.
Yeah, of course.
[UKA]
See ya!
[door opens and closes]
[insects chirping]
[UKA]
Summer break's almost over.
-Huh?
-I wonder how Miura's doing.
[STUDENT 8E] Look at those
hot guys over there!
They're totally
checking us out.
[STUDENT 8G] Hey.
You should go talk to them!
[STUDENT 8E] The blonde guy
especially is such a snack.
[STUDENT 8F] Right?
He's like a celebrity.
Leave it to Kai
to get girls lookin' our way!
Easy to pick 'em up.
Where's my food?
[STUDENT 8C]
Yeah, yeah, we know.
[sighs]
[STUDENT 8A]
Back to school next week.
[STUDENT 8B]
Got anything left to do?
-[STUDENT 8A] Homework.
-[STUDENT 8B] I feel that.
[STUDENT 8C] You, Kai?
Any unfinished business?
Yeah.
Huh?
[STUDENT 8A]
Dude, where are you going?
[STUDENT 8C]
We're not done here!
Hey.
I heard that
he rejected Serina.
What?
Who'd do that?
Guys like Kai.
Wonder if he has his sights
on someone else.
[UKA]
Oh.
There it is.
Mom said she wanted
to pick up this book.
[gasps]
♪
"On the Arrangement
of Succulent Plants."
Hm.
[chuckles]
Not even a smile?
[UKA]
He's here.
With me!
[ice clatters]
[UKA]
I can't believe it.
I'm having drinks with him!
Maybe it's been a while.
Or maybe I missed him.
But he looks even more
handsome than usual.
[gasps]
What?
I apologize.
[KAI]
How are things?
Good. And with you?
-[KAI] Good.
-That's good.
[KAI] Been looking
for a chance to ask.
How'd it go with those
three punks back at the beach?
[UKA]
You were watching?
Well, I was just asking
how things had been.
-[KAI] Look at you.
-And then?
I asked Remi
why I hadn't seen her at school
and she said that
she dropped out a while ago!
[KAI]
Yeah.
[UKA]
You already knew?
Yeah.
Swung by her class to see
if she felt bad,
but she wasn't there.
I can hardly believe it.
I had no idea.
[KAI]
That's right.
The old you would've known.
You would've been obsessed.
You would be petrified
of what's gonna happen next.
So it's great
you hadn't heard.
Means you're moving on
and your old bullies
can't bother you anymore.
[REMI]
Still, not like I give a damn.
[UKA]
I guess the same goes for me.
But actually...
I've been like that
for a while.
They haven't bothered me
since junior high.
They haven't been around.
[UKA]
No. More than that.
All my attention's been on you
and becoming a better me.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
[UKA]
Huh?
Why does he look so happy?
So, been hangin' out
with the girls?
-[UKA] Not yet.
-Any reason?
I'd like to find the chance,
but I'm still trying
to figure out
what they could stand
to gain hanging out with me.
What?!
I'm just afraid.
If they're with me,
is that the most
valuable use of their time?
[UKA]
There I go again.
Sure.
Least it's valuable to me.
[gasps]
You're always
overthinking things.
You're friends, aren't you?
Yeah!
That's a good point!
[sighs]
Yo, Kai!
Ready to go?
I didn't know
you were out with friends!
Well...I'm off.
Hey. Make sure you finish that.
♪
[UKA]
Wait! His number!
If I don't get it now,
I might not
before the end of vacation!
-Hey, we found a girl.
-Ooh.
You boys weren't
kidding about your friend!
Hey, gimme your number.
-[UKA] No.
-We can have fun.
[UKA]
I need to get it first!
-[STUDENT 8H] So?
-Miura!
Please, can I get your number?
[gasps]
Who's this chick?
Ugh.
[insects chirping]
[panting]
You finally asked, eh?
[gasps]
It's about time.
Glad it's not just me.
We both want to.
[gasps]
Go without me.
Yeah, yeah.
-Keep it real.
-[STUDENT 8H] Aw.
♪
[KAI]
Gimme your phone.
Oh, right!
♪
Ah. No, wait a second!
Did I mess up?
-[laughs]
-Maybe not?
On socials?
[UKA]
I mean, I know what they are.
Wanna try?
Is this a smartphone?
A what?
Maybe.
I never actually had
a phone before high school.
My dad bought it.
No sweat.
Let's just text for now.
♪
When you get home,
ask your dad
if you can download an app.
♪
[UKA]
He really gave me his number.
[KAI] I assume you won't text
till I text first.
-Nuh-uh!
-When?
♪
[UKA]
In case of emergency?
That's fine.
But you should
stand tall from now on.
Be more fearless
than ever before.
Okay?
And whenever things
do go wrong, tell me.
[KAI]
I'll be there in a heartbeat.
Sound good?
Yeah!
[UKA] [giggles]
It's slow.
But steadily,
my world is changing.
[UKA]
I'm back!
Welcome home.
Well, you sure look happy,
don't you?
Yeah, I bumped
into a few friends
from my school there.
[UKA'S DAD]
That's great.
So, uh...
-Hey, Dad?
-Welcome home, sweetie!
If you were going out
shopping,
you should've asked
your dad to drive you.
Those books must've been heavy!
[chuckles]
[UKA'S DAD]
You know I offered.
She said no.
Like how we can't take her
to the beach
or to see fireworks these days.
But it's okay.
You went with your friends
this year, right?
That's wonderful.
Although it makes me
a bit lonely.
At some point,
my little girl grew up
and stopped
holding her dad's hand.
[UKA'S MOM]
Oh.
[UKA]
Slowly...
but steadily.
♪
TO BE CONTINUED